

PROFILE

I am an experienced software developer with a demonstrated history of working in the industry as a full-stack web developer. I am skilled in Python, JavaScript, Java, and Web Frameworks. I have a great interest in Machine Learning and I am doing the best to learn it myself and enjoy while I do it!

CONTACT



+61 451 454 944



hello@abhisheksatpathy.com



abhisheksatpathy.com



linkedin.com/in/abhisat



github.com/abhisat

SKILLS

PROFICIENT:

Python JavaScript Java

Web Frameworks

LEARNING:

C++ ReactJS Data Pre-processing Tensorflow Machine Learning Deep Learning

ABHISHEK SATPATHY

Web Designer | Software Developer | Machine Learning Enthusiast

EXPERIENCE

PACE PROJECT TEAM MEMBER

Pepper Financial Services Group | March 2017 - Present

- Building an automated data retrieval system with a GUI for retrieving data from a Data-warehouse and converting the data into a standard Machine Learning usable format such as a .csv file.
- Gaining skills in pre-processing data in large data-warehouses and make it usable for ML classifiers.

WEB DEVELOPER

PCX Pty Ltd | Nov 2014 - Present

- Worked on the design and development of a Ruby on Rails cloud print website while acquiring the necessary skills on the go.
- Learned all the skills needed for full-stack web development like Rails development, website deployment, and PostgreSQL database administration along with skills like jQuery and HTML5 Canvas image processing.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

City University of Hong Kong | Apr 2014 - May 2014

• Experienced working with professional tools like Adobe Illustrator while creating event artwork for the Alumni Relations Office at City University.

STUDENT INTERN

City University of Hong Kong | Mar 2014 - May 2014

· Designed and published an iBook from the content and materials provided by the supervisor. Worked in a team of 4 and gained valuable team work experience.

EDUCATION

MACQUARIE UNIVERSITY

2014 - Present | Expected Graduation - Dec 2018 Bachelor of Engineering, Major: Software Engineering

LANCASTER UNIVERSITY

Michaelmas Term 2016 - 2017 | Study Abroad Courses: Advanced Programming, Artificial Intelligence, Internet Applications Engineering, Project Management Tools and Techniques

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

MACQUARIE UNIVERSITY VICE-CHANCELLOR'S INTERNATIONAL **SCHOLARSHIP**

Apr 2014 | Full-Tuition Scholarship

6.00.1X: INTRODUCTION TO COMPUTER SCIENCE AND PROGRAMMING USING PYTHON Apr 2014 | edX Certificate

6.00.2X: INTRODUCTION TO COMPUTATIONAL THINKING AND DATA SCIENCE Jan 2017 | edX Certificate

REFERENCE

PROF. DEBORAH RICHARDS

Department of Computing, Macquarie University

deborah.richards@mq.edu.au +61-2-9850-9567